2026 at
this point?
And I know
there's a lot
there's a
in your research,
but is there
your research,
a best idea
or narrative?
best idea
Just quickly,
if you could.
so the top
three stocks in
three stocks
our flagship
are Tesla.
We think it
has miles to
has miles
go. We do
take profits from
take profits
time to time,
time to
but it could
break out here
break out
in a big
way as more
and more analysts
more analysts
do their homework
on robotaxis.
their homework
Mm. Crispr
Therapeutics has moved
into the
second position.
That company is
curing sickle cell
curing sickle
disease and
beta thalassemia
and has its
eyes set on
has its
not just rare
not just
diseases, but curing
the bad cholesterol
problem, especially
for those
who have
hereditary issues
in that realm.
That could be
an enormous market,
enormous market,
and I don't
think anyone